I step off the train
I'm walking down your street again
And past your door, but you don't live there
anymore
It's years since you've been there
And now you've disappeared somewhere, like outer space
You've found some better place
And I miss you, like the deserts miss the
rain
Could you be dead?
You always were two steps ahead, of everyone
We'd walk behind while you would run
I look up at your house
And I can almost hear you shout down to me
Where I always used to be
And I miss you (like the deserts miss the rain)
Back on the train, I ask why did I come again?
Can I confess, I've been hanging round your
old address?
And the years have proved
To offer, nothing since you've moved
You're long gone, but I can't move on
And I miss you (like the deserts miss the rain)
And I miss you, yeah (like the deserts miss the rain)
And I miss you
I step off the train
I'm walking down your street again
And past your door, I guess you don't live
there anymore
It's years since you've been there
And now you've disappeared somewhere, like outer space
You've found some better place
And I miss you
You found some better place
And I miss you (like the deserts miss the rain)
And I miss you, yeah (like the deserts miss the rain)
And I miss you, and I miss you
(Like the deserts miss the rain)
And I miss you, yeah (like the deserts miss the rain)
The deserts miss the rain
(Like the deserts miss the rain)
Like the deserts miss the rain
And I miss you, yeah (like the deserts miss the rain)